明晚我要跟我爸一起吃饭 你要来吗？
Hey,I'm having dinner with my dad tomorrow night. Do you wanna come?
好啊，他很性感
Sure,yeah. He's kind of sexy.
不，我也会去
Oh,no,I'll be there too.
那么我们得想个暗号 如果一切进行的很顺利，你可以离开
So we'll come up with some kind of signal. If it's going well,you can take off.
不，我要你去那里支持我 我还没有告诉他我怀孕了
No,I just need you there for support. I haven't told him that I'm pregnant yet.
为什么？
Oh. Why not?
因为我知道他会气炸了 我讨厌让他生气
Because I know he's gonna flip out,and I hate it when he's angry.
瑞秋，这好像 “爸爸别说教”
Rachel,this is all so "Papa Don't Preach."
不，菲比，等一下，他是个可怕的人 有次他抓到我抽烟
No,Phoeb,wait. He's a scary guy. I mean,one time he caught me smoking.
他说如果他再看到我抽烟 他会逼我吃下一整盒烟
He said if he ever saw me doing that again,he'd make me eat the entire pack.
我一定会去
Wow. Well,I will be there.
天啊，我不会让那个男人 逼你吃掉你的宝宝
Gosh,I'm not gonna let that man make you eat your baby!
那个家伙是谁？ 我想我认识他
Hey,who is that guy? I think I know him.
才怪
No,you don't.
天啊，莫妮卡 他是你单身女郎派对上的脱衣舞男
Oh,my God! Monica,he's the stripper from your bachelorette party!
什么？
Her what?
你的秘密单身女郎派对
Your secret bachelorette party.
-你办了单身女郎派对？ -她用牙齿解开他的丁字裤
-You had a bachelorette party? -She untied his G-string with her teeth.
快来个人阻止我
Somebody stop me!
我们不办单身汉或单身女郎派对 我们都同意那是愚蠢的传统
We weren't having bachelor,bachelorette parties. We agreed that it's a silly tradition.
那是个很棒的传统
It's a grand tradition!
抱歉，她们给我一个大惊喜 我真的没有办法
I'm sorry. They surprised me. There was nothing I could do.
你可以用手解开它
Well,you could've untied it with your hands.
这太不公平了 我想帮我最好的朋友办单身汉派对…
This is so unfair. The one thing I wanted was to throw my best friend a bachelor party..
却不能那么做 我们只能一起去吃牛排
but I wasn't allowed. All we got was a stupid steak dinner.
你跟女服务生一起回家
You went home with the waitress.
对，那一晚真的很美妙
Yeah,that was a pretty good night.
我不敢相信你没有告诉我
I can't believe you didn't tell me.
你知道在婚姻里 开放跟诚实是很重要的
You know that the two pillars of marriage are openness and honesty.
我就知道送你那本书 有一天我一定会被报应
I knew giving you that book was gonna come back and bite me in the ass.
本集播出：脱衣舞娘
The.One.With.The.Stripper
主演：珍妮佛安妮斯顿
主演：寇妮考克斯
主演：丽莎库卓
主演：麦特勒布兰
主演：马修派瑞
主演：大卫修蒙
-我帮大家点了摩洛哥鸡肉 -我不吃肉
-I'll order everyone the Moroccan chicken. -Oh,I don't eat meat.
它是鸡肉
It's chicken!
-我也不吃那个 -我一直都搞不懂女同志
-I don't eat that either. -I never understand you lesbians.
-宝贝，告诉我你有什么事 -事实上…
-So,baby,tell me,what's new with you? -Well,actually..
你的74年拉菲红酒（国际葡萄酒五大名品之一）
Your '74 Lafite,sir.
我点的是75年的红酒 它的味道很棒，74年的酒就像阴沟水
I ordered the '75. That's a magnificent wine. The '74 is sewage!
你为什么要给我阴沟水？
Why would you bring me sewage?
那是个难题吗？你是白痴吗？ 所以你才会来当服务生吗？
Is that a hard question? Are you an idiot? Is that why you're a waiter?
那就是为什么我告诉经理 我不想为你服务的原因
This is why I told the manager I wouldn't wait on you.
少来了，别那么幼稚
Oh,come on. Don't be such a baby.
你应该注意到了 他真的很可怕
In case you didn't notice,that is a scary man.
但他说的对 74年的酒真的很难喝
He's right,though. The '74 is absolute piss.
这是个天大的错误 菲比，我不敢告诉他
This was such a huge mistake. I can't tell him,Phoebe. I can't.
瑞秋…
Rachel..
我得等上几年 然后宝宝会告诉他
I'm gonna wait a couple of years,and then the baby will tell him
-为什么？让他可以对宝宝生气？ -那是宝宝的问题
-Why? So he can get mad at the baby? -Hey,that is the baby's problem.
-服务生没问题吧？ -我不知道，我只是去了洗手间
-Everything okay with the waiter? -I have no idea. I went to the bathroom.
亲爱的，你得告诉我 最近你有什么新鲜事
So,sweetie,you were starting to tell me what is new with you.
我有TIVo啊（互动式数字录放影机）
I got TiVo.
-什么是TIVo -就是怀孕的意思
-What's TiVo? -It's slang for "pregnant."
菲比
Phoebe
不然你约我来做什么？
Well,what were you thinking asking me to come?
你真的怀孕了？
Are you really pregnant?
对跟不对
Well,yes and no.
除了，不是不对
Except,not no.
所以，对
So to sum it up,yeah.
孩子的爸爸是谁？ 不，拜托，别告诉我就是她
Who is the father? Oh,no. Please don't tell me it's her.
不，是罗斯，你喜欢罗斯
No,it's Ross. It's Ross. You like Ross.
爸爸 我希望你能接受这件事
Daddy,I hope you're okay with all of this.
想一想，这是件好事 这是你第一个外孙
Think about it. This is a good thing. This is your first grandchild!
你要当外公了
You're gonna be a poppy!
没错，我要当外公了
That's true. I'm a poppy!
我要当外公了
I'm gonna be a poppy!
-婚礼什么时候举行？ -谁的婚礼？
-So when is the wedding? -The who?
婚礼 你们得举行婚礼
The wedding. There's going to be a wedding.
小姑娘，你休想坐在那里告诉我 我的第一个外孙会是个私生子
Young lady,don't you sit there and tell me my first grandchild is gonna be a bastard!
-告诉我你们会举行婚礼 -二月二日
-Tell me there's gonna be a wedding! -February 2nd!
今天去看你上课我觉得很酷
It was cool seeing you lecture today.
谢谢，虽然我觉得 你看起来像是睡着了
Thanks. Although it kind of seemed like you were falling asleep.
不，我闭上了眼睛 要专心听你说话
No,I had my eyes closed so I could concentrate and,you know,take it all in.
我很多学生都会那么做
Yeah,a lot of my students do that.
-我得走了 -今晚见？
-I've got to get going. -Okay,I'll see you tonight?
谢谢你让我参观你收集的半珍贵的宝石 它真的很棒
Thanks for showing me your semiprecious-stone collection. It's amazing.
天啊，你的床上功夫一定很厉害
My God,you must be good in bed.
你跟蒙娜交往了一阵子 情况如何？
So you and Mona,it's been a while now. How's it going?
很不错
It's good. It's going good.
我们处得很好 她很…
I mean,we get along great. She's so..
-辣？ -我本来说很温柔，但你答对了
-Hot? -I was gonna say sweet,but yeah!
她能接受宝宝的事？
She's okay with the baby?
我还没有告诉她 我不想吓跑她
I haven't actually told her yet. I don't wanna scare her off.
你得老实说，不然的话 你以为你们的方向一样…
You have to be honest. Otherwise,you may think you're going down the same path..
事实上你们在走 不一样的路
but you're really going down different ones.
我会拿那本书 把你打死
I'm gonna take that book and I'm gonna beat you to death with it.
天啊 你一定会爱死我了
Oh,my God,you are gonna love me so much.
很好，因为到目前为止 在这段婚姻里我真的很喜欢你
Oh,good. Because so far in this marriage,I just like you a lot.
好吧，关于单身女郎派对的事 我真的很难过…
All right. I felt bad about the bachelorette party thing..
所以今晚 你要办单身汉派对
so tonight you're gonna have a bachelor party.
我在餐厅的同事给我这个电话号码 我雇了一个脱衣舞娘来跳舞给你看
I got this number from this guy at work and I hired a stripper to come dance for you.
我可以进太太名人堂了吧？
Am I going in the wife hall of fame or what?
-亲爱的，这太疯狂了，我不要脱衣舞娘 -你能让她说完吗？
-Honey,that's crazy. I don't want a stripper. -Will you let the lady talk?
来吧，一定会很好玩的 它会让我觉得好过一点
Come on,it'll be fun. It'll make me feel so much better.
我帮你们准备了派对帽跟喇叭
I got you party hats and porn.
抛开我爸爸 跟魔术师上床那段不谈…
Throw in my father making out with the magician..
这简直就像 重演我14岁的生日派对
and it's just like my 14th birthday all over again.
听着，我很感激，但它有点可怕 我已经不是单身汉了
Look,I appreciate it,but it's a little creepy. I'm not a bachelor anymore.
别把它当成是单身汉派对 把它当成是结婚两个月的礼物
Don't think of it as a bachelor party. Think of it as a two-month anniversary present.
当然，结婚一年是纸婚 两个月的话可以看热舞
Sure. One year is paper,but two months is lap dance.
拜托，我觉得好难过 去看看那个辣妹脱光衣服吧
Please,I feel so bad. Just watch the hot woman get naked!
-好吧，但我这么做是为了你 -太棒了
-Fine,but I'm only doing this for you. -Yeah!
还有乔伊
And Joey.
-谢谢，你还想邀请谁？ -光罗斯跟乔伊就够丢脸了
-Thank you. Who else do you wanna invite? -Ross and Joey is embarrassing enough.
抱歉，我没办法去 今晚我跟蒙娜有约
Actually,sorry,I can't even make it. I'm seeing Mona tonight.
谁会为了假单身汉派对 取消真正的约会？
Who would cancel an actual date just to go to a fake bachelor party?
抱歉 我得取消今晚的约会，宝贝
I'm sorry. I gotta cancel tonight,baby.
抱歉我无法参加你想像出来的婚礼 那天我很忙
I'm sorry I won't make it to your imaginary wedding,but I'm busy that day.
我得参加独角兽受洗礼 跟小精灵的犹太成年礼
I already have a unicorn baptism and a leprechaun bar mitzvah.
我知道，我乱了方寸
I know,I know. I panicked.
我不要他对着我大叫 把我当成74年拉图红酒（国际葡萄酒五大名品之一）
I didn't want him to start yelling at me like I was some '74 Latour.
是拉菲
It's Lafite.
74年拉图红酒 喝起来真的很不错
The '74 Latour is actually drinking quite nicely.
好吧，他来了，我得告诉他 我得很坚强
All right,here he comes. I'm gonna tell him. I'm gonna be strong.
我刚刚打了电话给一个朋友
I just called a friend of mine.
我想或许我可以 在这么短的时间内订到广场饭店
I think I may be able to book The Plaza on short notice.
真的吗？
Really?
广场饭店？
The Plaza?
爸爸
Oh,Daddy!
-爸爸，我得跟你谈一谈 -什么事？宝贝
-Right. Daddy,I need to talk to you. -What is it,sweetie?
我们不会举行婚礼 罗斯跟我不会结婚
There's not gonna be a wedding. Ross and I aren't getting married.
-对不起，爸爸 -我不敢相信
-I'm sorry,Daddy. -I don't believe this!
-爸爸，请保持冷静 -你怎么能要我保持冷静？
-Daddy,stay calm,please. -How do you expect me to stay calm?
我完全无法接受，瑞秋 我要知道为什么
This is unacceptable,Rachel. And I wanna know why!
因为那个混蛋 不愿意娶你吗？
Is it because that punk won't marry you?
-是那样吗？ -对，他说我是瑕疵品
-Is that it? -Yes. He says I'm damaged goods.
快结婚了你很紧张吧？
You nervous about getting married?
你在做什么？
What are you doing?
我们假装这是你结婚前的 单身汉派对，那样比较好玩
Let's pretend it's a real bachelor party,before your wedding. It'll be more fun.
好吧，我不敢相信 明天是我的大喜之日
All right. I can't believe tomorrow's the big day.
知道你永远无法跟别的女人在一起 你有什么感觉？
How's it feel knowing you're never gonna be with another woman?
知道你每天醒过来 都会看到同一张脸…
Knowing you're gonna have to wake up to the same face every day..
直到死神 来拯救你
until you finally have the sweet release of death.
你说的对，这样比较好玩
You're right. This is more fun.
她来了，快点
That's her! Okay,come on!
哪个幸运儿是钱德？
Which one of you lucky boys is Chandler?
是我
That's me!
That's me.
乔伊崔比亚尼，你的头号仰慕者
Joey Tribbiani. Big fan.
-那是卧房吗？ -对，就在那边
-Is that a bedroom? -Yeah,right over there.
好吧，你准备好就进来
All right. Whenever you're ready.
那好奇怪
That was weird.
-她为什么要到卧房去？ -我在等着
-Why would she go in the bedroom? -I'm waiting.
-她是… -她是脱光衣服的妓女
-So she's a.. -Yeah,that's one naked hooker.
我喜欢你家 这玩意从哪里来的？
I love your place. Where is this guy from?
那是在加尔各答买的 18世纪印度工艺品
That's an 18th-century lndian artifact from Calcutta.
哇
Oh. Wow.
原来你不只懂恐龙的事
So you're more than just dinosaurs.
一点都没错
So much more.
天啊，我很抱歉
Oh,my God! I am so sorry!
不用管，那是在皮尔第一进出口公司（著名的工艺品杂货店）买的
Forget it. It's from Pier 1.
抱歉
Sorry.
你以为你可以搞大我女儿的肚子 然后不娶她吗？
You think you can knock up my daughter and then not marry her?
我要杀了你
I'm gonna kill you!
事实上 我现在真的很不方便
You know,this is actually not a great time for me.
快一点 解释给我听，盖勒
So come on. Explain yourself,Geller.
-你先让我的瑞秋怀孕 -你让瑞秋怀孕？
-First,you get my Rachel pregnant. -You got Rachel pregnant?
-谁干的？ -就是你
-Who did? -You did!
没错，但那是一夜情 那毫无意义
Yes,I did,but it was a one-night thing. It meant nothing.
真的吗？ 我女儿对你来说毫无意义？
Oh? Really? That's what my daughter means to you,nothing?
不是的，她对我来说意义重大 我在乎…我爱瑞秋
No,sir. She means a lot to me. I care.. I love Rachel.
-什么？ -但不是那样的
-What? -But not that way.
我没有爱上她 我把她当成朋友
I'm not in love with her. I love her like a friend.
你就是那样对待朋友的吗？ 你搞大她的肚子又不肯娶她？
That's how you treat a friend,get her in trouble and refuse to marry her?
我有跟她求婚 但我不想那么做
Hey,I offered to marry her. But I didn't want to.
为什么？ 因为你想跟这个荡妇鬼混？
Well,why not? So you could spend your time with this tramp?
荡妇？
Tramp?
抱歉，格林医生，蒙娜 蒙娜，格林医生
I'm sorry. Dr. Green,Mona. Mona,Dr. Green.
我不敢相信 里面有个脱光衣服的妓女
I can't believe there is a naked hooker in there!
或许她是妓女 兼脱衣舞娘…
Maybe she's a hooker and a stripper..
但她会搞不清楚该做什么
but she got confused about what to do.
有可能，技术上来说她脱光了衣服 只是我们没看到
Could be. I mean,technically,she did strip. We just missed it.
小姐
Ma'am?
你也是脱衣舞娘吗？
Are you also a stripper?
不是，但我可以假装 那得另外收钱
No,but I can pretend to strip. But that's gonna cost extra.
这是另外收钱的项目 手铐，鞭打…
Okay,here's the extras: handcuffs,spanking..
或许莫妮卡是在跟你开玩笑
Maybe Monica's playing a joke on you.
帮自己老公找妓女 那真的很好笑
Getting her own husband a hooker. That's pretty funny.
那很好笑，或许我生日的时候 她会去杀人
That is funny. Maybe for my birthday she'll murder someone.
我敢说罗斯也知情 他“刚好”很忙
I'll bet Ross was in on it too. I mean,he was "conveniently" busy.
-你不介意我抽烟吧？ -事实上我想…
-Do you mind if I smoke in here? -Actually,I'd rather..
抽吧，反正 我们会烧掉那个房间
Yeah,go ahead. We're gonna have to burn that room down anyway.
-你为什么一直没有告诉我？ -我打算告诉你，但是…
-How could you have kept all this from me? -I was going to tell you,but..
你以为你可以得到你要的 然后像甩了瑞秋一样甩掉她
You figure you'd get what you wanted,then you'd dump her like you did Rachel.
我没有甩掉瑞秋 我们也没有在一起
Hey,I did not dump Rachel. Nor are we still together.
我可以…
Can I..?
让答录机接吧
Why don't we just let the machine get that.
罗斯，我是乔伊 这里有个妓女…
Hey,Ross,it's Joey. There's a hooker over here..
我们想或许你知情
and we thought maybe you'd know something about it.
不
No! No! No!
No!
我需要躺一下
I need to lie down.
大伙们，我能跟你们谈一下吗？
Hey,guys,can I talk to you for a minute?
听着，我要你们推销鸭肉特餐…
Listen,again,I want to urge you to push the duck special..
因为如果客人不吃鸭肉 你们得吃，它不是很好吃
because if they don't eat the duck,you're going to,and it's not very good.
今晚是单身汉派对之夜？
Tonight's the night of the big bachelor party?
-谢谢你给我那个女孩的电话号码 -别客气，谁要办派对？
-Thanks for giving me that girl's number. -No problem. Say,who's the party for?
-我老公 -你帮你老公雇了一个妓女？
-For my husband. -You hired your husband a hooker?
-她是脱衣舞娘 -不，她是妓女
-She's a stripper. -No,she's a hooker.
-他们有时这样称呼脱衣舞娘？ -因为她们是妓女
-Is that what they call strippers sometimes? -When they're hookers.
天啊 史都，我不敢相信你会这么做
Oh,my God. Stu,I can't believe you did this.
你确定她是妓女？
Now,you're sure she's a hooker?
如果不是的话 她是我约过最棒跟最贵的女孩
It's either that,or she's just the best,most expensive date I ever had.
或许她是故意帮你雇了个妓女
Maybe she meant to get you a hooker.
她为什么要那么做？
Why would she do that?
或许她要你好好学一学
Maybe she wants you to learn something.
你在床上表现的不好吗？
Is there anything you're really bad at,you know,sexually?
这是最糟糕的单身汉派对
This is the worst bachelor party ever.
-你们怎么那么久？ -再一分钟就好
-What's taking you boys so long? -In a minute!
“一分钟”？ 一分钟内会发生什么事？
"In a minute"? What's gonna happen in a minute?
好吧 或许你该去请她离开
All right. Maybe you should ask her to leave.
-为什么是我？ -这是你的单身汉派对
-Why me? -Hey,it's your bachelor party.
-所以应该是你去说 -我不要，你去
-Which is why you should do it. -I don't want to. You do it.
好吧，剪刀石头布 决定谁去请那个妓女离开
All right. Rock,paper,scissors for who has to tell the whore to leave.
-什么？ -我想念这个
-What? -I miss this.
我想我们以前 没有这么做过
I don't think we've actually done this before.
不，我想念跟你鬼混的日子
No,I miss hanging out with you.
-我们还是混在一起 -跟以前不一样了
-We still hang out. -Not like we used to.
还记得吗？你跟我 我们以前老是粘在一起
Remember? You and me,we used to be inseparable.
现在一切都变得不一样了
You know,now it's like things are different.
一切的确不一样了 我结婚了
Well,you know,things are different. I'm married now.
别误会我 我为你们感到高兴
And,hey,don't get me wrong,I am so happy for you guys.
我只是想念我们一起 鬼混的日子，你知道吗？
I just miss hanging out. Just us,you know?
我也是
Yeah,I miss that too.
听我说，从现在开始 我们找时间一起出去
I'll tell you what. From now on,we'll make time to hang out.
你说的对，过来
You got it. Come here.
天啊
Oh,God.
听着 我差一点就要洗劫你们了
Listen,I am this close to robbing you guys.
她是妓女 她是…
She's a hooker! She's a hooker! She's a..
嗨，我们通过电话
Hi. We spoke on the phone.
你爸到过我家
So your dad dropped by.
他是个好人
He's a pleasant man.
-不 -我得走了
-Oh,no. -I better go.
我只是要到这里来 我不想错过吵架场面
Just over here. I don't wanna miss the fight.
罗斯，我很抱歉
Ross,I am so sorry.
我发誓明天我会亲自 跟他把事情讲清楚
I promise,I will straighten this out with him tomorrow,in person.
或是透过电子邮件
Or via e-mail.
我不在乎你爸，我在乎蒙娜 当时她在场，她气疯了
I don't care about your dad. I care about Mona. She was there and she's freaked out!
好吧，我也会跟她解释 告诉我她的电子邮件信箱
Okay,I'll fix that too. What's her e-mail address?
我发誓我会解决的 我发誓我会跟她说
All right,I promise,I'll fix this. I swear. I'll talk to her.
好吧，谢谢你
Okay. Thank you.
就那样？ 你们说那是吵架？
That's it? You call that a fight?
“我们当时分手了”，“不，我们没有” 你们两个是怎么了？
"We were on a break!" "No,we weren't!" What happened to you two?
谢谢你答应回来
Thank you so much for coming back over.
很好，你在这里
Oh,good. You're here.
我很担心 这会是个不愉快的经验
And I was worried that it was going to be uncomfortable.
不，蒙娜，听我说
No,Mona,just hear me out.
首先我很抱歉 我爸对你大叫
First of all,I am so sorry about my father yelling at you.
但我听说你控制住自己的脾气 你得告诉我你是怎么做的
But I heard that you held your own. You have to tell me how you did that.
-说重点 -好吧
-Focus. -Okay.
罗斯跟我以前交往过
Yes,Ross and I used to date.
我们的确有宝宝了
And yes,we are gonna have a baby.
但我们绝对 不可能复合
But we are definitely not getting back together.
-我怎么能相信你的话？ -因为我们把彼此逼疯了
-How can I be sure of that? -Because we drove each other crazy.
他占有欲很强，爱吃醋 他从来不会忘了那些小事
He was possessive,he was jealous. He could never just let the little things go.
试着去跟这个女人交往吧
Trying to date this woman.
但那都比不上 他的温柔体贴…
None of that compared to how kind and gentle..
跟善良
and thoughtful he is.
或许你不该碰我
You probably shouldn't touch me.
我不想介入 这么复杂的事
I don't wanna get in the middle of something so complicated.
我明白，但是蒙娜 哪段感情不复杂呢？
I get it,but,Mona,what relationship is not complicated?
我们都有自己的包袱 你也一样
We all have our baggage. You must too.
不然你为什么还是单身呢？
Why else would you still be single?
我得走了
I'm so gonna leave right now.
我应该让门开着吗？
Should I leave this open?
我还不确定 你为什么不告诉我？
I'm not sure yet. Why didn't you just tell me about all this?
因为那跟我对你的感觉 没有关系
Because what's going on has nothing to do with how I feel about you.
-你还是应该告诉我 -我知道，我打算那么做…
-You still should have told me. -I know,and I was going to..
但我想最好 还是让瑞秋的爸爸来告诉你
but I thought it was better that you heard it from Rachel's father.
我犯了一个错…
I made a mistake..
但那是因为 我真的很喜欢你，真的
but it's only because I really,really like you. Really.
好吧，我想 你可以把门关上了
Okay. I guess you can close the door now.
我忘了拿皮包 你们和好了
Forgot my purse. Oh,you guys made up.
他是接吻高手，对吧？ 我要走了
He's a good kisser,isn't he? I'm going!
我发誓我不知道她是妓女
I swear I didn't know she was a hooker.
你让她在这里抽烟？
Did you let her smoke in here?
你奶奶的被单上还有她的屁股印子 你真的想谈抽烟的事？
Her ass-print is still on your grandmother's quilt. Really want to talk about smoking?
你知道吗？ 我要补偿你
You know what,I'm gonna make this up to you.
我答应要帮你请脱衣舞娘…
I promised you a stripper..
我一定会做到
and you're gonna get a stripper.
-莫妮卡，等一下 -什么？
-Monica,wait. -What?
继续
Carry on.
这双网球鞋好紧
These tennis shoes are so tight.
-我想把它们脱掉 -麻烦你别说话
-I think I'll take them off. -Could you not narrate?
知道了，水手
Gotcha,sailor.
只因为你不爱这个家伙…
Just because you're not in love with the guy..
-你跟你爸说实话了 -大约是一小时前
-You told your dad the truth. -About an hour ago.
-你想去看电影吗？ -好
-Wanna go see a movie? -Yes.
再见，爸爸
Bye,Dad.
我无法接受 爱跟这件事有什么关系？
It's unacceptable! What the hell does love have to do with it?
还有比爱 更重要的事
There are more important things than love.
你得考虑宝宝
You have to think about the baby.
你得想想 你做的决定会有什么后果
You have to think about the consequences of your decisions!
我的确会想 我做的决定会有什么后果
Hey,I do think about the consequences of my decisions!
你有什么权利…
Well,what gives you the right to..?
去死吧
Go to hell!
电话里的笨男人
Stupid guy on my phone.